欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
《比利小子》前情提要
Previously, on Billy the Kid.
我跟你一个好朋友一起骑马放牛
I'm ridin'with a good friend of yours.
-你认识杰西吗 -我当然认识
You know Jesse? - Sure I do.
我决不离开
- I will never leave!
不 不 不
No! No, no, no.
你要逮捕我
You're arrestin' me?
布雷迪治安官只想和你谈谈
Sheriff Brady just wants to talk to ya.
是我们的老板 墨菲市长让我过去的
Major Murphy, our boss, told me to go up there.
我别无选择 只能开枪
I had no alternative but to shoot.
所以算是正当防卫
So it was self- defense?
他也许会离开一段时间
Maybe he goes away for a while.
重新学习 以执法者的身份回归
Gets re- educated. Comes back out the other side as a lawman.
比利和德尔·托博斯科的女儿杜尔西内亚
Billy got real friendly with Del Tobosco's daughter,
关系很好
Dulcinea.
卡特隆先生如果想要我的财产
If Mr. Catron wants my belongings,
我的牛 马 都可以给他
everything, my horses, my cattle he can have them.
让开
Get out of the way.
你们都是一群魔鬼
Devils, all of you! -
他们杀了所有人 比利
They killed everyone, Billy.
杀了我全家
My whole family.
其中一个持枪歹徒假扮成了你 比利
One of the gunmen pretended to be you, Billy.
我会为你家人报仇的 我发誓
I will avenge your family's death, I swear.
这里为什么这么多人
Why are all these men here?
因为我们要接管这个镇了
Because we're gonna take over the town.
林肯县人民早已厌倦了没有王法
The people of Lincoln are tired of the lawlessness...
一片混乱的世界
...and the chaos.
他们想要改变 是时候了
They want change. Now is the time.
我之前不理解你为什么要开战
I told you I didn't understand why you needed to go to war.
现在理解了
Now I do.
胡安·帕特隆在很多人心中
Most of you will also know Juan Patron
都是西班牙裔社区的领导者
as a leading member of the Hispanic community.
地位十分重要
He's very important.
It's an honor, Billy.
这是约翰·威尔逊法官 比利
This is Judge John Wilson, Billy.
就是他签发了约翰·汤斯顿谋杀凶手的
It was he who issued the warrant for the arrest
逮捕令
of those responsible for John Tunstall's murder.
看来还是有人站我们这边的
So after all, there are people on our side.
麦克斯文先生 你需要配枪吗
Mr. McSween, would you like a gun?
我做了这么久的牧师早已立誓
I was a pastor all these years and Ive sworn off
不再用枪了
ever using a gun myself.
你好 曼纽拉
Hola, Manuela.
这位是杜尔西内亚·德尔·托博斯科女士
This is Senorita Dulcinea Del Tobosco.
她需要一个安全之暂避
She needs somewhere safe to hole up for a while.
不知能否住你这里
I'm hoping she can stay here with you.
卡特隆先生刚刚任命了
Mr. Catron has just appointed
林肯县的新任治安官
a new sheriff in Lincoln County.
他誓要把每一个不法分子和枪手
A sheriff who's pledged to drive each and every gunman
赶出这片土地 恢复法律和秩序
and outlaw out of this territory and restore law and order.
我建议你和他合作
I suggest you co- operate with him.
你和我 是合作伙伴
You and me, we're partners here
我恨不得现在就把
and all I want is nothing more
那个该死的比利小子
than to see that Billy the fuckin' Kid
送上绞刑架
hangin'on the end of a rope.
杰西
Jesse.
请坐吧
Take a seat.
最近怎么样
Hw you gettin' on?
还行吧
All right.
忙着任命副手
Sworn in my deputies.
熟悉新的职责
Gettin'to know my way around.
你呢 找到比利了吗
What about you? You any closer to findin'Billy?
在努力了 找到些线索
Tryin". Had some leads.
他应该把老巢撤了很远
Reckon he pulled his camp way back, out of the way.
你觉得他是想干什么
What do you think he's planning to do?
想想他最不可能做什么
Think about the most unlikely thing,
也许就是他的一下计划
that's probably what he'll do.
比如呢
Like what?
他一直处于守势 被动挨打
He's been on the defensive. He's reacting to things.
以我对他的了解
My guess?
他宁愿主动出击
He'd rather be on the offense.
不然他知道自己会被围剿殆尽
Otherwise, he knows he's going to get hunted down.
因此 我们最好保持警惕
We best be vigilant, then.
这样吧 我可以给你分点人手
You know what? Ican spare you some of my men
一起追捕他
to help with your hunt for him.
我们要保证对他的压制
Got to keep the pressure on him.
谢谢 很感谢
Thanks. Appreciate that.
但不得不说 看你戴着治安官警徽的样子
I gotta say, it's strange seeing you
感觉很奇怪
with that sheriff's badge on.
我已经不是之前那个我了 杰西
Things were very different back then, Jesse.
我当时很迷失 HERI
I was a lost soul.
找不到方向
Didn't know which way to turn.
你有过这种感觉吗
You ever felt that way?
应该没有过 治安官
I can't say I have, Sheriff.
一个人出生 然后某天
You're born, and one day...
这个人死去
- ...you die.
仅此而已
That's all.
祝你一天愉快
I wish you a good day.
好 这个镇子归我们接管了
AlI right. We're takin over the town.
我们会恢复林肯的法律和秩序
We're gonna restore law and order in Lincoln,
但要先干掉浩世才行
but we have to take out The House to do it.
我们要沿着主街进发
We're gonna ride in hard through Main Street,
然后兵分三路
splitting into three smaller groups
一路拿下沃特利酒店
to take the Wortley Hotel,
一路拿下汤斯顿商行
the Tunstall Store.
一路负责胡安和墨西哥分队 你们负责镇中心
Juan and the Mexicans, you'll take the downtown area.
抢占以下战略位置 就能对浩世集团形成夹击
From these strategic positions, I believe we can cut off
把他们赶出镇子
the house and drive'em out,
解放林肯的人民
liberating the people of Lincoln
把这里变成净土
and makin' the town safe.
我们只要当心加勒特治安官就行
We just have to watch for Sheriff Garrett.
他那边什么消息
I don't have a read on him yet.
我们只知道 他把几个手下借给了杰西
Yeah, well we do know that he's lent Jesse
他们正在全县范围内
a couple of his deputies, and they're
搜寻我们
searching the county for us right now.
所以我们更要转战下一个城镇
That's another reason for moving into town now.
好的 让我们开始吧
Right. Let's get to it.
我们上
Let's go.
枪战开始时一定要保持警惕
我觉得他们会把我们逼到镇广场
你派几个人过来
So have a few of your men come through
从山坡上包抄他们
and flank 'em from the hillside.
好的比利别担心
-照顾好自己 朋友 -你也是 我的朋友
大家各就各位 快
Everyone to your positions. Go!
-乔治 去屋顶 -好的
George, take the roof. On it.
到底是怎么回事
What the hell's goin'on here?
对不起 山姆
I'm sorry, Sam.
我们需要暂时接管你的酒店
We're talking over your hotel for a while.
保护好他们 小子们
Keep'em safe, boys.
威尔逊法官发给国会议员的
What happened with the letter
那封信情况如何了
that Judge Wilson sent to the congressman?
沃伦·安吉尔还在调查事实的阶段
Warren Angel has yet to complete his fact- finding mission.
但他发布了一份中期报告
But he's issued an interim report
表明他已经发现阿克塞尔总督
which suggests he's already uncovered possible evidence
和托马斯·卡特隆存在潜在腐败
of corrupt and illegal activities
和违法行为的证据
by both Governor Axtell and Thomas Catron.
所以你是说我们这次还有
So you're sayin' there's still a chance the law
讨回公道的可能
could be on our side?
也许吧
Maybe.
可我不这么想 比利
But I wouldn't count on it, Billy.
我们不能坐以待毙
You know, we can't wait for it.
我们在做对的事 麦克斯文
We're doing the right thing here, McSween.
该来的终于来了
我们现在要为自己而战
为了我们的自由
注意安全
Watch yourself.
准备上了 小子们
Be on your ready, boys.
你们要干什么
What do you want?
我们已经接管了这个镇子
We've taken over the town.
我们想给大家一个
We want to give you all a chance
自由选择离开的机会
to get out before it's too late.
如非必要 我们不希望发生枪战
We don't want a gunfight if we don't need one.
我们只是来恢复和平的
We're just here to restore the peace.
我得先问问莱利先生的意见
Well, uh, we're gonna have to talk to Mr. Riley about that.
你可以去问莱利先生
You talk to Mr. Riley, Mr. Murphy,
问任何一个有权关店的人都行
anybody else who might bring this business to a close.
我们就在这儿等着
Until then, we're not going anywhere.
把门关上
Close that fuckin door.
他们刚说什么
- What did they say?
他们说已经接管了小镇
They uh, they said they'd taken the town,
请我们马上离开
and they want us to leave right away.
接他妈的管 他们在骗你们
The hell they havel They're fuckin' lying.
而你们却像枪靶子一样站在这儿
And you're standing here like patsies.
比利小子就在外面
Billy the Kid's right fuckin' down there.
开枪 超他开枪 射死他
Shoot him. Go ahead, shoot him!
去啊 小子们
Come on, boys.
砸碎窗户 嘿
Smash the windows! Hey!
当心
Watch out!
查理
Gharlie!
找掩护 查理
Take cover, Charliel
该死
- Goddamn!
他们要跑了
They're on the move!
上马
Get on!
我们走
- Let's go!
快走 小子们
口 - Go, boys. Go!
驾
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
你他妈看我干什么
What the fuck are you doin' lookin'at me?
派人过去 去找其他人
Get some men down there, find the others.
我要知道到底发生了什么
I need to know what the fuck is happening.
-没问题 莱利先生 -除了这个你还会说啥
Sure thing, Mr. Riley. - "Sure thing, Mr. Riley. "
见鬼了
Oh, for fuck's sakes.
准备好了吗
You ready?
他们就要来了
They'll be comin'soon.
拐角处
On the corner.
他拿枪指着乔治
He's got a gun on George.
把枪放下
Put that rifle down!
他们不会停的 比利
They ain't stopping, Billy.
比利 注意右侧
Billy, on your right!
找掩护
Take cover!
后门有人过去
Coming around the back way!
快 快 快
Go, go, go, go!
芜湖 我们成功了
Woo- hoo! Yeah, we did it!
我做到了
I did it!
让他们都去死
Send"em all to hell!
嘿 别碰死人
Hey. Don't touch the dead.
为什么
Why?
闭嘴 好吗
Shut the fuck up, will ya?
这不是打游戏 进屋
This ain't a game. Get inside.
大家都守好自己位置
Everybody, back to your stations.
嘿 出什么事了
Hey. What's goin'on?
莱利先生
Mr. Riley.
你他妈的去哪儿了
Where in the fuck were you?
看来管理者
It would seem that the Regulators
已经控制了墨西哥区和镇中心的大部分地方
control most of the downtown and the Mexican quarter.
杰西还在外面找比利小子么
Jesse's still out lookin'for The Kid?
对 我已经叫他马上回来了
Yes, and I've asked him to come back immediately.
而与此同时呢
And in the meantime...?
我把我副手派来 他们一到
I'm calling in my deputies. As soon as they arrive,
就让他们去汤斯顿商行
I'll send them to the Tunstall Store.
莱利先生 擒贼
If you need to kill a snake, Mr. Riley,
先擒王
you gotta cut off its head.
听着 你现在不能惊慌
Look, I advise you not to panic at this point.
也许你不信
It may not look like it,
但最好的牌依然在我们手上
but we still hold all the best cards in the pack.
驾 驾
·Hup, hupl·Hyah! Hyah!
脚印朝北 通向南泉牧场那边了
Tracks are leadin' north to the old South Spring Ranch.
-去树林 -驾
·To the woods! ·Hyah! Hyah!
乡亲们 你们出城去会更安全
Folks, you'll be safer outta town.
只是暂时待几天
It's just for a few days.
你可以坐马车跟孩子一起走 好吗
You can take the wagon with the kids, okay?
我们很快就会回来
I know we'll be back soon.
别担心
Don't worry.
退后 伙计们
Stand down, boys.
苏
Sue!
我一定要过来帮忙
I had to come and help.
谁能帮我把桌子搬到这
Can someone please move these tables here?
好
All right.
给我准备点淡水
I need some fresh water.
再帮我找几条毯子可以吗 谢谢
Can you please find me some blankets? Thank you.
先生们 这种徽章有背后的涵义
Gentlemen, these badges mean something.
好吗 这是荣誉徽章
Okay? They're badges of honor.
现在 你们每个人都背负着维护法律
Now, all of you have been given the great responsibility
履行正义的巨大的责任
of upholding the law and administering justice.
在这艰难的时刻
These are difficult times.
你们需要勇气和毅力
You will need courage and fortitude,
但我相信你们
but I am placing my trust in you,
我也知道你们不会让我失望
and I know that you will repay it.
现在
Now...
谁对自己的枪法有信心
which ones of you consider yourselves to be good shots?
好
All right.
我要你们三个在日出之前
I want you three to take up positions
沿着城镇的边缘驻扎
along the edge of town before sunrise,
一直延伸到汤斯顿商行附近
by the Tunstall Store.
而其余的人要在城中所有
And I want the rest of you to go surround
监管者的驻扎点戒备包围起来
the Regulators' positions downtown.
但你们不要一股脑儿地过去
But I want all of you to move in a wide circle.
他们会到处搜寻你们的
They'll be lookin' for you.
所以别被任何人发现
So don't let anyone see you. You understand?
好 很好
Good. Good.
小心屋顶上的枪手
Watch out for those shooters on the roof.
结论就是
nal word? -
嘿 比利
Hey, Billy.
他们这下知道我们来了
Well, they know we're here now. -
我们今天杀了他们一个出其不意
We caught them by surprise today,
但明天 他们会加倍小心
but tomorrow, they come back twice as hard.
我猜 他们一定会先派神枪手
My guess is first thing, they'll be sharpshooters
埋伏到镇上
around the town.
赫雷拉
Herrera.
胡安说你是他的得力干将
Juan says you're his best shot.
好吧 那你需要证明自己
All right. First thing, you prove it.
你另带四个人 占据屋顶位置
You take four others, and you find rooftop positions
千掉那些神枪手
and you take out those sharpshooters.
剩下的人请记住 就算他们要
The rest of you just know that if they try
正面进攻 也是我们火力占优
a head- on attack, we have more firepower.
太对了
Damn right.
好了 大家都去睡觉吧
AII right, everybody get some sleep.
明天还有一场硬仗
We're gonna need it.
查理 你来第一个值班
Charlie, you take first watch.
杜尔西内亚
Dulcinea?
怎么了
Yes?
你在想什么
我的家人
全被他们全杀了
我还是不敢相信
再也回不到从前了
全都变了
一切
我很抱歉 杜尔西内亚
为你的失去和痛苦而抱歉
现在 连比利也要死了
这要由上帝决定
我有时真希望他们把我也杀了
他们似乎已经走了
Looks like they cleared out.
等等 等等
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
比利已经接管城镇
Billy's taken over the town.
小子们 咱们回到后面去
Boys, let's get back there!
驾 快来
Hyah! Hyah! Come onl
那是汤斯顿的狗
It's Tunstall's dog.
麦克斯文
McSween.
过来 小家伙
Here, boy.
来吧
Come on.
来了 小子们
Here we go, boys!
谷仓里有枪手
Shooters in the grainery!
一起上
Together!
这帮孙子打不过我们
These bastards can't stop us!
-没事的  -二楼
- It's okay. It's okay. - On the second floor!
趴下 小子们
Stay down, boysl
下一个
There next!
注意转角处
找掩护
我打中了
咱们走 咱们去那边
都安全了
All clear!
我必须承认 你们能来真是太好了
I have to say, I'm mighty glad to see you folks.
加勒特治安官的副手
Well, you know, Sheriff Garrett's deputies
从北边突袭了汤斯顿商行
are attacking Tunstall's store from the north side.
已经把比利和大部分头目困在了里面
They've got Billy and most of the leaders holed up inside.
他们都是敌人 而且说白了
They're the enemy. To be frank,
为他们卖命的墨西哥人也死不足惜
the Mexicans working for them are worth nothing.
下次你就该跟我们一起去 莱利先生
Maybe you should come down there with us, Mr. Riley.
胡安说他们已经把那些副官
Juan tells me they cleared the deputies
赶到了镇子外围 所以
from the bottom of town, so...
那个区域目前掌握在我们手里
at this moment, we control that area.
而且我们还控制着汤斯顿商行
And of course we control the Tunstall Store
及周边地区
and the surrounding area.
但是时候转守为攻了
But it's time to stop defending and start attacking.
明天中午
Tomorrow, at noon,
胡安会带着手下加入我们
I want Juan and his men to join us here,
我们要一起冲进墨菲的商行
and together, we'll storm the Murphy Store
把莱利及其团队赶出镇子
and drive Riley and his men out of town.
大家同意吗
We in agreement?
莱利先生 你手里有钱
Mr. Riley, you have the money.
应该用它来买更多的武装
You can put up so we can hire more guns.
约翰·肯尼还有一天半才能到
John Kenny's a day and a half away.
我们需要面对现实
We need to face facts!
管理者和墨西哥人组成了
The Regulators with the Mexicans
60人左右的精锐部队重要部队
constitute a significant force of around 60 fighters.
我们现在连三分之一都凑不够
Right now, that's a third more than we can muster.
-墨西哥人打仗 -莱利先生
·Mexicans as fighters- - - Mr. Riley.
更重要的是 先生们
What's more, gentlemen,
他们十几个核心成员都是一等一的
is their core consists of a dozen or more
神枪手
first- rate gunmen.
不光是比利小子
Not just Billy the Kid,
还有韦特 科尔 鲍德里等人
but Waite, Coe, Bowdre, and others.
他们不会善罢甘休
They're not gonna walk away.
治安官说得对
Sheriff's right.
只要比利小子想进攻
If The Kid wants it.
他就能找到我们
he knows where we are.
说的太对了
Yeah, damn right he does.
除非
Unless...
我们能逆天改命
we change the odds.
请稍等 治安官
Hold up, Sheriff.
达德利上校 这是新任治安官
Colonel Dudley, it's the new sheriff.
帕特·加勒特先生
Mr. Pat Garrett.
很抱歉这么晚打扰你 达德利上校
I'm sorry to call on you so late, Colonel Dudley.
首先 我
First of all, I, uh,
早就该来看望您以示敬意的
should have come up here sooner to pay my respect.
行嘞 治安官
All right, Sheriff.
阿克塞尔总督写信
Governor Axtell wrote me
跟我说你的当选
and told me about your appointment.
我想象得到 新上任这几天
And I can well imagine that these early weeks
压力一定不简单
have been trying ones.
来吧 请坐
Please, have a seat.
谢谢你 先生
Thank you, sir.
相信你一定知道
I'm sure you are aware
一群以比利小子为首
that a group of gunmen and thieves,
自称为管理者的
calling themselves the Regulators
持枪歹徒和小偷
and led by the outlaw Billy the Kid,
想要占领小镇
are trying to take over the town,
取消小镇的合法权威
remove its lawful authorities.
最近的杀人事件也因此激增
Recently, there has been a great increase in killings.
对 这些我都知道 治安官
Yes, I'm aware of all that, Sheriff.
在绝望之下 先生
Well, out of desperation, sir,
那些想要维护权威的人 包括我内
those lawful parties, myself included,
重组成为”法律与秩序党“
have reconstituted ourselves as the"Law and Order Party. "
我今晚是代表党来看您
And it is on behalf of that party
寻求您帮助的
I've come up here tonight to ask for your help.
好吧 你也不是林肯第一位
Well, you're not the first sheriff in Lincoln
请求军方援助的治安官了
to ask for the military's help.
事实上 美国宪法对军队的限制
The fact is, the U. S. military is severely constrained
很严重
by the Constitution
不得干涉地方和公民纠纷
from interfering with local and civic disputes.
坦白讲 我们在这的职责 是管控印第安人口
Quite frankly, were here to control the Indian population,
而不是给公民劝架
not feuding citizens.
我明白
I understand.
但目前林肯的情况
But, uh, what we have now in Lincoln
远超过公民纠纷
is not a civic dispute.
简直是屠杀和一片混乱
It's butchery and mayhem.
我恳求您快想想办法 以免为时已晚
I implore you to act before it's too late.
我手里有张阿克塞尔总督的公告
I have here a proclamation from Governor Axtell.
他命令所有武装人员就地解散
It commands all armed men to disband,
返回家园 不要在美国军队会出手的情况下
return to their homes, and not act as vigilantes
充当义务警员
so long as U. S. Army can be summoned.
所以
So...
上校 我是否可以理解成 您会
can I take it, Colonel, that you will interfere
代表执法机关来出手干预呢
on behalf of the forces of law and order?
不 加勒特治安官
No, Sheriff Garrett.
其实 我在这里的职责
You see, my job here
就是不断权衡 如果军队参予到公民社会中
is always to weigh out the advantages and disadvantages
会带来哪些利弊
of involving the army in civil society.
但我们一旦如此 就会招来
And when we do, we often earn the ill- will
大家的反感 治安官
of the population, and that, Sheriff.
所以说 这个问题很棘手
is a matter of great consideration.
我告诉你 你要是不马上插手
Let me tell you that unless you interfere right away,
林肯街上将会血流成河
there will be a massacre on the streets of Lincoln.
你不觉得这会给你和你军队的形象
Don't you think that will earn you and the Army
扳回一局吗
the ill- will of the people?
祝你晚上愉快
I wish you a good evening.
贝克维斯
Beckwith!
-贝克维斯 -在
Beckwith? - Yeah!
-油 -钉死了
Oil! - Hammer it in!
大家快点
Let's go! Let's go!
我会为你祈祷的 比利
I'|l pray for you, Billy.
我们决不投降
We must never surrender.
我现在相信了
I believe that now.
我们是在为事业而战
We're fighting for a good cause.
一项崇高的事业
A noble cause.
愿上帝赐予你胜利
May God give you the victory.
谢谢你
Thank you.
真希望能借你吉言
I do hope you're right.
所以
So...
你们要怎么做
What are you gonna do?
你觉得管理者真有那么强吗
Do you think the Regulators
能跑到这里打我们
are strong enough to attack us here?
没错 他们很强
Yeah, they are.
那你有何对策
Then what are ya gonna do?
莱利 稳住
Riley, steady.
我觉得你们最好来外面看看
I reckon you boys should take a look outside.
真厉害 加勒特治安官 真厉害
Good man, Sheriff Garrett. Good man!
达德利上校
Colonel Dudley.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你来得正是时候
You came just in time.
全体 立正
Company, halt!
别担心 治安官 这是我们职责所在
It's all right, Sheriff. Just doing our duty.
治安官
Sheriff.
你想逮捕哪些人来着
Which men do you want arrested, exactly?
我想逮捕他们全部
I want the whole damn business.
加勒特治安官 我把话说清楚
Sheriff Garrett, let me be perfectly clear.
我今天到林肯来 并不是要帮你们
I did not come to Lincoln today to assist you in any way.
我是来确保妇女和儿童安全的
I'm here to ensure the safety of the women and children.
男人的事 就让男人自己解决
The men can take care of themselves.
但我强调一下 要是有任何人
But if anyone, and I stress anyone,
朝我的军队开火
fires upon my company,
我会马上还击 明白吗
I will return fire immediately. Understood?
达德利上校 我是亚历山大·麦克斯文
Colonel Dudley, I am Alexander McSween.
我是管理者的律师
I act as attorney for the Regulators,
而管理者 是一群致力于终结林肯县的
those who are fighting for an end to corruption
腐败而斗争的人 看到您的部队
here in Lincoln. While I am gratified
愿意保持中立 我不胜感激
that your troopers will remain neutral,
我必须指出 在你的支持者中
I must point out that among those supporting you
有几人被指控谋杀了约翰·汤斯顿
are several men charged with the murder of John Tunstall
我有将其就地抓获的逮捕令
and for whose immediate arrest I carry warrants,
由法官约翰·威尔逊亲自签署
signed by a Judge John Wilson.
我还有抓捕布雷迪治安官谋杀案
And I have warrants for the arrest
凶手的逮捕令呢
of those responsible for the murder of Sheriff Brady.
有些凶手就站你面前 麦克斯文先生
Some of whom are standing right over there, Mr. McSween.
先生们 我今天不是要逮捕谁
Gentlemen, I am not here to arrest anyone today.
而是来恢复和平的
I came here to restore the peace.
我命令所有人马上回家
I am ordering all of you to go home, now.
立即离开
Leave immediately.
这个城镇将实行无限制宵禁
This town is under permanent curfew.
任何人未经允许
Find anybody out on the streets past hours
在街上逗留超过几小时
without permission or a damn good reason
就会被捕 都明白么
will be arrested. Understood?
清楚吗
Clear?
-副队呢 -明白
Lieutenant? - Sir.
骑兵 封锁城南
Cavalry, cordon to the south.
步兵小心疏散平民
Infantry, let's clear the civilians, gently.
好了 让我们为内森·达德利上校
AlI right, let's raise a glass to Colonel Nathan Dudley
和美国骑兵干一杯
and the U. S. Cavalry.
喝吧 小子们
Let's go, boys!
别忘了帕特·加勒特
And don't forget Pat Garrett.
他也是个好人 为帕特·加勒特治安官干一杯
He's a good man. Raise a glass to Sheriff Pat Garrett.
这是你的
That's yours.
你有什么想说的吗
So what do you gotta say for yourself?
你什么意思
Well, what do you mean?
问我什么意思
What do I mean?
帕特·加勒特救了你一次
Pat Garrett just about saved your ass.
而你连个屁都没放
You personally have done jack shit.
这就是我的意思
That's what I mean.
-怎么样 -他们在墨菲商行
Well? - They've put up their tents
南边的空地中搭了个帐篷
in a field just below Murphy's store.
他们赢了 墨菲和莱利 他们赢了
They've won. Murphy and Riley. They've won.
并没有赢 达德利上校才是这个国家真正的法律
No, they haven't. Colonel Dudley is the real law in this country.
我们跟他解释清楚就行
And when we explain to him- -
这不会有啥区别的 麦克斯文太太
It won't make any difference, Mrs. McSween.
上校发誓说 他不会偏袒任何一方
The Colonel swore he wasn't taking sides.
他只是来恢复和平的
He's only here to restore the peace.
也不知道出什么事了
I don't know what happened. I didn't think
军队都要介入降维打击
the army was gonna get involved.
他们不应该被牵进来的
They're not supposed to get involved.
真是出乎所有人意料
No one saw this comin'.
我没想到会这样
I didn't see this comin'.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
比利
Billy.
杰西在哪儿
Where's Jesse?
我不知道 怎么了
I don't know. Why?
马上离开 快点
Leave. Now.
我们得把你我二人的计划定好 眼下就是机会
We need to make plans. Now's our chance.
为什么
For what?
好做出新的行动
To make new moves!
-我会找到他的 莱利先生 -去找吧
- I'll find him, Mr. Riley. - Do.
你好啊 比利
Hello, Billy.
帕特
Pat.
很高兴见到你
It's good to see you.
真的吗
Really?
听着 我不想让你觉得
Look, I don't want you to think
我们两方是对垒关系
that we're on opposite sides here.
因为我们不是
Because we're not.
我想要你想要的东西
I want what you want.
怎么 你也想要正义
Oh, you want justice too?
我当然想要正义了
Of course I want justice.
你想要结束浩世 还是结束指环王
You want the end of the House? The end of the Rings?
这我控制不了 比利 我只是治安官
I can't control that, Billy. I'm just the sheriff.
作为治安官
Well, as just the sheriff,
你更应该在这件事上保持中立
I presume you're gonna stay neutral in this whole business
而不是总偏袒站错队的浩世
and not pick sides with the House.
比利 事情比这复杂多了
Billy, it is so much more complicated than that.
去他妈的
The fuck it is.
你不能与体制抗争
You can't fight the system.
这话说的对味了
And now we're talking.
如果没有法律 那就成了无政府
If there's no law, there's only anarchy.
这对谁都没有好处
And that is in no one's interest.
知道吗 我越来越觉得他是在背台词了
You know, that sounds like it's right outta their handbook.
比利
Billy...
你必须放弃
You have to give up.
你赢不了的
You can't win.
你什么时候才能明白 这对我来说不是游戏
When are you gonna learn this ain't a game for me?
我不在乎输赢
I don't care about winning.
我关心的只是 长久以来
All I care about is that for too long,
圣达菲的几个腐败混蛋
a few corrupt assholes in Santa Fe,
比如阿克塞尔和卡特隆
like Axtell and Catron,
掌控中林肯的一切
been pullin' all the strings down here in Lincoln,
把这些可怜人榨干
bleedin'these poor people dry.
只要有任何人站出来
And if they speak up, if anyone speaks up,
他们都会保持沉默
they're silenced.
要是学不会沉默 他们就会被暗杀
And if they can't be silenced, well, then, they're killed.
我们只想改变这一点 帕特
We're just tryin' to change it, Pat.
但我们需要你的帮助
But we need your help.
你曾被授予过徽章 说明你有这个能力
You have been given a badge. You have the power.
利用它吧
Use it.